{
    "studyset": "22867671",
    "data": [
    {
        "question": "a",
        "answer": "yī"
    },
    {
        "question": "about",
        "answer": "guān yú"
    },
    {
        "question": "all",
        "answer": "suǒ yǒu"
    },
    {
        "question": "also",
        "answer": "yě"
    },
    {
        "question": "and",
        "answer": "hé"
    },
    {
        "question": "as",
        "answer": "rú tóng"
    },
    {
        "question": "at",
        "answer": "zài"
    },
    {
        "question": "be",
        "answer": "shì"
    },
    {
        "question": "because",
        "answer": "yīn wèi"
    },
    {
        "question": "but",
        "answer": "dàn shì"
    },
    {
        "question": "by",
        "answer": "tōng guò"
    },
    {
        "question": "can",
        "answer": "néng"
    },
    {
        "question": "come",
        "answer": "lái"
    },
    {
        "question": "could",
        "answer": "néng gòu"
    },
    {
        "question": "day",
        "answer": "rì"
    },
    {
        "question": "do",
        "answer": "zuò"
    },
    {
        "question": "even",
        "answer": "shèn zhì"
    },
    {
        "question": "find",
        "answer": "zhǎo dào"
    },
    {
        "question": "first",
        "answer": "dì yī"
    },
    {
        "question": "for",
        "answer": "wèi"
    },
    {
        "question": "from",
        "answer": "cóng"
    },
    {
        "question": "get",
        "answer": "huò dé"
    },
    {
        "question": "give",
        "answer": "gěi"
    },
    {
        "question": "go",
        "answer": "qù"
    },
    {
        "question": "have",
        "answer": "yǒu"
    },
    {
        "question": "he",
        "answer": "tā"
    },
    {
        "question": "her",
        "answer": "tā de"
    },
    {
        "question": "here",
        "answer": "zhè lǐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "him",
        "answer": "tā"
    },
    {
        "question": "his",
        "answer": "tā de"
    },
    {
        "question": "how",
        "answer": "zěn me"
    },
    {
        "question": "I",
        "answer": "wǒ"
    },
    {
        "question": "if",
        "answer": "rú guǒ"
    },
    {
        "question": "in",
        "answer": "zài"
    },
    {
        "question": "into",
        "answer": "jìn rù"
    },
    {
        "question": "it",
        "answer": "tā"
    },
    {
        "question": "its",
        "answer": "tā de"
    },
    {
        "question": "just",
        "answer": "zhǐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "know",
        "answer": "zhī dào"
    },
    {
        "question": "like",
        "answer": "xǐ huān"
    },
    {
        "question": "look",
        "answer": "kàn"
    },
    {
        "question": "make",
        "answer": "zuò"
    },
    {
        "question": "man",
        "answer": "nán rén"
    },
    {
        "question": "many",
        "answer": "hěn duō"
    },
    {
        "question": "me",
        "answer": "wǒ"
    },
    {
        "question": "more",
        "answer": "gèng duō"
    },
    {
        "question": "my",
        "answer": "wǒ de"
    },
    {
        "question": "new",
        "answer": "xīn"
    },
    {
        "question": "no",
        "answer": "bù"
    },
    {
        "question": "not",
        "answer": "bù"
    },
    {
        "question": "now",
        "answer": "xiàn zài"
    },
    {
        "question": "of",
        "answer": "de"
    },
    {
        "question": "on",
        "answer": "zài"
    },
    {
        "question": "one",
        "answer": "yī"
    },
    {
        "question": "only",
        "answer": "zhǐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "or",
        "answer": "huò zhě"
    },
    {
        "question": "other",
        "answer": "qí tā"
    },
    {
        "question": "our",
        "answer": "wǒ men de"
    },
    {
        "question": "out",
        "answer": "chū"
    },
    {
        "question": "people",
        "answer": "rén"
    },
    {
        "question": "say",
        "answer": "shuō"
    },
    {
        "question": "see",
        "answer": "kàn jiàn"
    },
    {
        "question": "she",
        "answer": "tā"
    },
    {
        "question": "so",
        "answer": "suǒ yǐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "some",
        "answer": "yī xiē"
    },
    {
        "question": "take",
        "answer": "ná"
    },
    {
        "question": "tell",
        "answer": "gào sù"
    },
    {
        "question": "than",
        "answer": "bǐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "that",
        "answer": "nà"
    },
    {
        "question": "the",
        "answer": "de"
    },
    {
        "question": "their",
        "answer": "tā men de"
    },
    {
        "question": "them",
        "answer": "tā men"
    },
    {
        "question": "then",
        "answer": "ránhòu"
    },
    {
        "question": "there",
        "answer": "nà lǐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "these",
        "answer": "zhè xiē"
    },
    {
        "question": "they",
        "answer": "tā men"
    },
    {
        "question": "thing",
        "answer": "shì qíng"
    },
    {
        "question": "think",
        "answer": "xiǎng"
    },
    {
        "question": "this",
        "answer": "zhè"
    },
    {
        "question": "those",
        "answer": "nà xiē"
    },
    {
        "question": "time",
        "answer": "shí jiān"
    },
    {
        "question": "to",
        "answer": "dào"
    },
    {
        "question": "two",
        "answer": "èr"
    },
    {
        "question": "up",
        "answer": "shàng"
    },
    {
        "question": "use",
        "answer": "shǐ yòng"
    },
    {
        "question": "very",
        "answer": "hěn"
    },
    {
        "question": "want",
        "answer": "xiǎng yào"
    },
    {
        "question": "way",
        "answer": "fāng shì"
    },
    {
        "question": "we",
        "answer": "wǒ men"
    },
    {
        "question": "well",
        "answer": "hǎo"
    },
    {
        "question": "what",
        "answer": "shén me"
    },
    {
        "question": "when",
        "answer": "shén me shí hòu"
    },
    {
        "question": "which",
        "answer": "nǎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "who",
        "answer": "shéi"
    },
    {
        "question": "will",
        "answer": "huì"
    },
    {
        "question": "with",
        "answer": "yǔ"
    },
    {
        "question": "would",
        "answer": "huì"
    },
    {
        "question": "year",
        "answer": "nián"
    },
    {
        "question": "you",
        "answer": "nǐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "your",
        "answer": "nǐ de"
    }
]
}
